<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Wenlong Liu&#39;s website</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Wenlong Liu&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Wenlong Liu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brief introduction of storm hysteresis effects in solute concentration-stream discharge (C-Q) relationship</title>
      <link>/post/brief-introduction-of-storm-hysteresis-in-solute-concentration-stream-discharge-c-q-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/brief-introduction-of-storm-hysteresis-in-solute-concentration-stream-discharge-c-q-relationship/</guid>
      <description>What are storm hysteresis effects? Generally, in order to investigate the dynamics of stream discharge and solute concentrations (C-Q relationship) in a watershed, researchers and environmental engineers usually set up monitoring stations in the watershed outlet. As the temporal dynamics of discharge and solute concentration is an integration of complex hydrological and biochemical processes, the relationship between solute concentration and discharge, hereafter called C-Q relationship, is mostly non-linear. If we plot the concentration against discharge within one storm event in a plot, we are supposed to see a non-linear loop, instead of a linear regression curve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hellow world!</title>
      <link>/post/brand-new-personal-website-of-wenlong-liu-powered-by-hugo-academic-and-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/brand-new-personal-website-of-wenlong-liu-powered-by-hugo-academic-and-blogdown/</guid>
      <description>Since Jan. 2018, my brand new website is published online. The website is powered by Blogdown and Hugo-academic, and deployed by Github Pages. All the codes are open to public and available at my github repository.
I build this website to achieve two goals: helping others know more about my professional achievements, and presenting my most latest output (with details) to persons of interest. Therefore, I will list my publications, including journal articles, conference presentations and proceedings, and book chapters (if any) here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>